Breaking
news... The President
will be making an
official statement
regarding the rising
assault and murder rate
as well as the rapidly growing
gas shortage across America.
But for now. sit back. relax.
and enjoy this 1960s classic.
I don't want to sound
morbid. I-I really don't.
But statistically speaking.
this is good for us.
Hmph.
When people are
scared. they panic.
Panic equals accidents...
Which means cha-ching.
I was gonna say it presents
a valuable opportunity
for us to do our jobs.
- Yeah.
- That's why she's the boss.
In all fairness. though.
Simon's not wrong.
I mean. the board's bursting.
And if Gina can handle
the call volume...
Jas. you might
finally take him down.
Probably just in her dreams.
It's happening.
Um. I heard people
are. uh. attacking people.
Like... Like. out of
nowhere. Going crazy.
Scratching. biting...
I mean... Joel. whatever's
happening can't be worse
than what you and your wife did
at last year's Christmas Party.
That is a burn. Joel.
Speaking of parties.
Brian wants industrial-chic
at the reception.
Like. Wimbish House
is nice. but...
Gina. is there something
you want to say
about my wedding venue?
Circle of Trust...
Here. now. and always.
Uh. please hold.
There's a fender bender
on Glenwood and Haas.
This keeps up. new faces on the
board at the end of the day.
Bonuses for top sellers.
What about incentivizing
nervous patrons?
Yes. incentivize nervous patrons
to upgrade their policies.
Circle of Trust...
Here. Now. and...
Uh.
please hold.
Circle of Trust. Please hold.
Thank you for
holding.
Circle of Trust...
Here. Now. and...
Uh. please hold. One moment.
Uh. I'm
passing... Circle of Trust.
It's the media.
Hype.
People need to chill.
The CDC is freaking next door.
If anything was really
wrong in the hospitals
or wherever. they'd
be all over it.
Everybody's fine.
Except for Gina.
She's beyond help.
Ooh. that... that look.
She's gonna bite!
Aah.  Okay.
Let's get to work. people.
Gina...
Please hold... I'm heading out.
Please forward my calls
and stay at your desk
till everyone leaves.
The back door wasn't
locked on Monday.
And order more mugs.
They keep disappearing.
Forward your calls. lock
the door. order mugs.
Got it.
Bye. everyone!
Upgrade policies.
Higher umbrella.
Happy weekend!
"At the edge of life and death.
a dark wave spreads
across the brain."
No.
We're on vacation. Blair.
Okay. right.
Jekyll Island. just you and
me. swimming with sharks.
Atlanta is experiencing
a catastrophic gas shortage.
resulting in mass lines
forming around the city.
The mayor asks
everyone to remain calm
in these trying times...
Ah. finally. here we go.
I think our receptionist
is stealing my coffee mugs.
It's gotten worse over
the last six months.
She's like this completely
incompetent mute
who just. like. stares
at me all day long.
Like a stalker.
Are you nuts?!
We're at a gas station.
What the hell?! See?!
This is exactly what
I was talking about.
Talking about what?
Blair.
This doesn't look
like the office.
Oh. I. um... No. I...
I wasn't leaving.
I was just getting a
snack because our...
You know. our vending
machine is broken. and. um...
I-I'll be back in a second.
I don't know what to say. Gina.
Asking you to do
your job is baseline.
Everyone else does
what's expected.
I think we might have to
reassess your position.
I'm sorry. Are you firing me?
Wow. Gina.
You can't even follow
one simple directive.
That sure is a lot of
stuff for two nights.
Brian and I have a long weekend.
Yeah.
We're not leaving leaving.
It's just a little
weekend getaway.
While I stay till 6:00 to make
sure the back door is locked.
Someone has to!
Don't walk away from me. Gina!
It's your job!
I'm serious.
Gina. this was a long time
coming. and I'm sorry.
but. yes. you're fired.
I'm calling Jasmine.
Oh. my God.
Where is the driver?
Has anyone seen the
driver of this car?!
Oh. my God. I have
to get out of here.
What the hell?!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Gina. why do you have a
shotgun in your trunk?!
I-I'm sorry.
I need your truck.
Uncouple the hose.
No. it's not safe.
Well. then. figure
it out. please.
Uncouple the hose.
No.
Gina. what the
hell are you doing?
Gina: Joel was right. asshole.
Ma'am. I'm an agent
with the Department
of Homeland Security
here in Atlanta.
There's no need to panic.
Put the gun down.
You seem like a nice girl.
Nice girls shouldn't be pointing
shotguns at oil tankers.
All due respect.
you don't know me.
Give me the keys.
Now! What?!
Gina. listen to the agent.
Let me help. miss.
No. listen. she's
mad because of me.
Gina. I won't fire you. okay?
I promise.
Put the gun down.
'Cause you want to go
back to your normal life
with your normal job.
Blair. you don't
know me. either.
Give me the gun. Wendell.
bud. get in the tanker!
Sir. under DHS code
82a. section 12.
I will be confiscating
this tanker.
Dad. behind you!
Like hell you are!
Shit!
I don't want to sound morbi...
You okay?
Yeah. it's just a...
A coffee ground.
Maybe someone else should make
the coffee in the morning.
I made the coffee this morning.
Uh. you... you were saying?
I was saying...
Right. I was saying.
uh. it's morbid...
No. I mean. panic.
Panic.
Panic is good.
S-Statistically speaking.
For... For business. I mean.
Yeah. nervous people.
they... They overreact.
and. um. cortisol levels
and stress hormones...
These hormones...
Circle of Trust.Um...
Accidents. insurance.
There's a fender
bender... Please.
Hold the calls for a second.
Please hold.
Y-You're not worried?
No.
I...
The only thing I'm
worried about is Gina.
What do we really know
about Gina anyway?
Maybe she's a...
A serial killer.
Maybe she's a bank robber.
What?
Maybe she's hiding a
shotgun under her desk.
Ooh!
Stay back.
She's gonna snap!
Circle of Trust. Please hold.
What?
How would you like me
to direct this call?
Jasmine. Joel. Simon...
You know what to do.
You're awesome. Get to it.
See if you can up
people's policies.
Take advantage of the
fear porn going around.
Okay.
I'm heading out.
A long weekend with Brian.
Please stay at your desk this
time and forward my calls.
This time?
Yeah.
You're never at your
desk when we need you.
It's going to be
a... A very busy day.
Also. be sure to lock up
after everyone leaves.
The back door wasn't
locked on... on Monday.
The back door
wasn't locked on Monday.
That can't happen again.
Are you... Are you
taking glassware home?
What?
Just order more mugs.
We're running short.
Hey. honking at
people is your job.
What's going on with you?
Um...
Nothing. I'm fine.
You're quiet.
So?
You're never quiet.
I'm. um...
I'm... I'm kind of freaking out.
Um...
Don't.
We'll be on an island.
Things will blow over
by the time we're back.
No. Um...
I'm...
Have you ever had. uh. déjà vu?
Like. really bad déjà vu?
Eh. that's just the mind.
Neurons firing too fast.
Yeah. right.
Neurons.
Breathe.
Aah!
Hey. what are you doing?
Where are you going?
Hey!
Uncouple the hose.
Gina! Do it.
I don't know what
the hell is going on.
but you're gonna get us killed
just like you did last time!
Give me the keys... now!
Gina. I-swear-to-Jesus.
Keys.
Stay put. Agent.
Please.
It's
too much truck for you.
Oh. is it too much truck for me?
One gun around a
tanker's bad enough.
Do you know that
woman? Not very well.
She's my receptionist. and
she's clearly lost her shit.
You need to talk her down.
We don't have time for games.
Oh. my God. it's real.
Wait. Time? What do you...
What do you mean time?
Oh. my gosh! I'm so sorry!
Oh. that must hurt.
I'm very sorry!
What is she doing?
Stay there! What?
Just leave it alone!
Stop! DHS is
ordering you to stop!
I will shoot! You can't.
You'll blow us all up.
Bitch.
Blair!
Gina. stop!
I'm sorry.
Gina?
What's up with her?
Nothing.
Everything.
It's happening to
you. too. isn't it?
What the hell is going on?
That man...
he was really... He
was eating that woman.
He was eating her.
I know.
The NSA guy...
DHS. What?
Department of Homeland Security.
He alluded to something
bad. like. um...
Like we're running out of time.
Um. and now we're... we're what?
We're repeating it.
It's happened to
you twice. right?
Are we dead?
Maybe this is a dream.
Um. have you heard of this
thing called morphic resonance?
It's... What are you doing?
No. We have to
talk about this.
We have to figure it out.
I just wanted a snack.
How is that an
acceptable answer?
No sane person would
respond to this situation
with "I just wanted a snack."
The vending machine is broken.
I've mentioned it a few
times to you. but...
you're always busy.
It's always broken.
And I... I wanted a snack.
I was hungry because
I forgot my lunch.
So I went to the gas station.
That's what you
want to talk about?
The damn vending machine?!
Gina?!
Gina!
No!
I don't want to talk abo...
I don't want to talk
about anything with you!
I don't want to talk...
Go to the gas station.
don't go to the gas station.
I won't be at the gas station.
Just...
Just leave me alone!
Leave me alone. Blair!
What the hell?
I know. we've been
waiting forever.
Are you seeing this?
Gina: Get up! Oh. my God.
It's like a movie.
Uncouple the hose.
Is this staged?
Is it loaded?
She can't be for real.
Oh. who knows anymore?
She's an asshole.
Don't get out of the car. Blair.
You could get shot.
It doesn't matter.
What are you doing?
Trying to save our lives!
Give me the keys!
We've already done this!
Ugh!
What?
I thought you said you
weren't coming back!
Well. that's before I blew
a tire and had to come back.
I had to...
Give me the keys.
Now!
That bite looks bad.
Don't ask me how I know.
I just do.
I need you to tell
me what's going on.
Why are you so desperate
to get out of Atlanta?
Things are bad.
Very bad.
People are going crazy.
clawing and biting each other.
The military has
taken over the city.
closing roads as we speak.
They're only keeping
two backroads open...
Route 122 and The
Armuchee Byway.
Please. give me the keys now.
Ma'am. I'm with the
Department of Homeland...
I know.
I know who you are.
Hey. what
are you doing in here?!
Dad!  Wendell!
Oh. my God. He's in the truck.
Wendell!
Wendell! My son is in there!
Blair!
Blair! Get back in the car!
Hey! Hey. bud.
Everything's fine.
Oh.
You want to steer the wheel?
Huh? You can drive the truck!
Blair! Gina!
Get it together!
You've already
blown us up twice!
I can't get at the driver!
Wendell! Get the seat belt!
Wendell. can you get... Can
you get the seat belt...
Stop yelling at him. Blair!
Come on. girl. get it together!
Get the... Get the seat belt!
Wendell! Wendell. help us!
Help us!
It's okay. It's okay. honey.
Blair. I'm gonna take
my hand off the wheel!
No! I'm gonna open the door!
No! No. no. no. no!
I'm going! No!
You don't want to
sound morbid. but...?
Something is off.
The city isn't
telling us everything.
Have they ever?
He...
died.
I saw it.
And then. he came back.
He was dead. and
then he came back.
The rumors are true.
He was eating your shoulder
like he was starving.
Just. like. right
through your flesh.
Ugh. His eyes were so...
vacant.
Icy.
Why is this happening?
Great problem-solving.
Shut up.
This is happening because
you can't stop talking.
You talk and you talk.
and then.
when you're done with that...
you talk.
And somehow it's
always about you.
I... I can't take it anymore.
I can't hear your selfish voice
over and over and over again.
Do you think that they
actually like you?
Is that what you think?
They play nice. and they
listen to you drone on and on
about your life
so that they can get a
stupid picture on a wall!
You should hear the
shit they say about you.
Jasmine. go ahead.
Tell her how much
you hate her hair.
And your clothes.
How?
How are you wearing that
many neck accessories?
And do you know why the back
door is always open on Mondays?
Because Joel... it's okay...
Comes in early on Mondays so
he can leave early on Mondays
so that he can go see
his daughter play soccer.
Emmy. right?
Emily. Emily.
It's close.
But you would know any of
this if you took two seconds
to talk toand not ata
single person here!
Nobody cares about
your "spring nuptials."
We work at an insurance company.
Our lives suck.
Your life...
sucks!
So please do me a favor
and just...
mind your own business
and drive out of town
with your Ken doll.
and leave me alone!
And stop leaving your
dirty mugs on my desk!
Blair: I'm selfish?
You.
You're selfish!
If you had stayed at your desk
and just done your job.
this would never have
happened in the first place!
Talking about you being selfish
was one of the
first things I said.
So you didn't even listen
to the rest of it. did you?!
If she cared about
you even a little bit.
she would warn you
to get out of here.
I did this for Wendell.
And us.
What a hero.
You can thank me now or
send me a letter from jail.
Ma'am. this weapon isn't
registered in your name.
You want to tell me how
you come to possess it?
It's my brother's.
We live in a shitty
neighborhood. okay?
So. when he works graveyard.
I watch his girls.
Make sure that they
can't access it.
I keep it in the trunk.
We both know why you did this.
So the tanker wouldn't blow.
Yeah. so we can all
move on.
Ladies. you need to take
a step back from each other.
You must be neck-deep
in your own ass
if you believe your shit.
Ahh!
Stop coming to the gas station!
I wish I could!
Go to hell.
We're already there!
Having an illegal
gun is a felony!
That's enough!
Aah!
Ah!
Oh. I'm gonna give
you to Jasmine!
She hates it!
Ahh! Oh!
No. no. no. no. no.
Aah!
Blair!
Die!
Aah!
Uh. Gina. are you
gonna answer...
Nope. go ahead.
You know what I
keep thinking about?
His eyes.
They're gray.
Dead or alive.
they're always gray.
Wendell's little truck
has a Band-Aid on it.
Maybe he would've grown
up to become a doctor.
That woman screams the
same way every time.
Every time her husband comes
back to rip her face apart.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll go. I'll go.
Oof.
You okay?
Here. drink this.
Thanks.
Oh. my God.
You ever notice we
never make it to 5:00?
I hate this hour.
You think the next hour's
gonna be any better?
Probably not.
But at least it's
not rinse and repeat.
You keep trying to leave.
but the city is closing down.
The military is here.
Even if you try to leave.
you will never get out
unless you know
which roads to take.
You need me.
Let me go.
Please.
I didn't know what I was doing
when this whole thing started.
but now I just...
I want to get to my
brother and my nieces
and get the hell out of here.
and I need that oil tanker to
get us to where we need to go.
Where are your nieces?
Downtown. Washington Park.
That's suicide.
They're shutting down the city.
It's my family.
We have been at
this so many times.
so I'm just gonna say
what we both already know.
We're not gonna be friends.
You don't like me.
I don't like you.
It... And that's okay.
I...
Blair. you have Brian.
I need my family.
But I need you to
break the cycle.
Please...
stay in your car and let me go.
Blair.
Stop!
I will shoot!
Are you okay?
No.
But I appreciate your concern.
Even if you do hate my hair.
What?
I... like your highlights.
It's fine.
Let's close early.
Seriously? Yes.
Joel. you're right.
Things are much
worse than they seem.
You all should just go.
Blair. do you need
a Xanax. or...?
I'm not kidding.
Go.
But the phones...
It doesn't matter.
Leave. Hole up.
hoard... I don't know.
Just leave. Go.
Alright. If you... say so.
Yes. See you on Monday.
Sweetie. I'm on my way.
What are you doing? I've
been waiting for 30 minutes.
You know how insane traffic is?
You were really great...
when my dad died.
I'm so grateful for that.
Okay.
You're welcome.
Can we go?
At the gas station.
you never take more
than two steps out of
your car to help me.
Why?
Help you? What...
You watch me die
again and again.
Why?
What?
Blair... We shouldn't do this.
It's not right.
We're not right.
You're breaking up with me?
We're engaged. Blair.
We both know it. Brian.
We never were.
And time...
we just don't have enough
of it to do the wrong thing.
Just... Just go.
To the island. Be safe.
Not fast enough?
Just get it over with. Aah!
Aah!
Hey.
Everyone. ignore the calls.
We're closing early.
Go!
Gina. a minute.
You guys can answer
the phones. too. you know?
So. you were right.
I never even made it downtown.
What did you do?
I stayed here and got eaten.
It was the worst way to go.
I'm sorry.
Well...
I'm sorry for being such a
dick these past two years.
Really. I was just
insanely angry. and...
You obviously hated
me from day one.
and I just put it all on you.
That's not an excuse.
But I'm sorry.
Uh...
Well. thank you.
I mean. I...
To be clear. though.
I... I didn't hate you.
Yes. you did. It's okay.
I did. I hated you.
But you were...
You were annoying.
And bossy. Mm.
And incredibly selfish to
the point where I was like.
"What's happening?"
I retract the apology.
However. you are a
relentless bitch.
and as a judgmental
coward. I respect that.
You kind of forced me to
be a little less doormat-y.
and I keep dying a little less
pissed off at myself. so thanks.
That's. like. the
nicest. weirdest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Felt weird coming out.
I don't know how many
more times I can do this.
Mm.
Do you want to
try something new?
What are you thinking?
See that man?
He's one of those things.
He's gonna kill everyone here!
Don't move. or I
blow your head off.
She's a cold-blooded killer.
She's killed me at
least five times.
Thanks.
Stop! Stop right now!
Wendell! Get back!
Wendell! Wendell. get back!
Wendell!
What's wrong with that man?
Wendell. get back!
No.
You were supposed to stop him.
Get down!
Where am I going?
Washington Park. right?
Your nieces.
Take 85 into the city.
Get out at route 129.
Why did you go for this tanker?
Why not a Porsche?
You saw this thing blow.
Who's gonna mess with
a bomb on wheels?
Blair Crawford...
Nice to meet you.
You are a crazy bitch.
Compliment returned.
Plus. if it is the
end of the world.
gas is better than cash.
That's smart.
But not personable. Okay.
How did you end up at reception?
Um... it was supposed
to be temporary.
I. um... I went to
school for marketing.
but it wasn't Harvard.
and I didn't know any CEOs
growing up who could
get me in a door.
I got complacent.
Cowardly.
Yeah. My attitude didn't help.
Yeah.
But I could've
handled it better.
Well. I mean. you
did pull a shotgun.
Well. not on you.
Oh. my God. Your face.
Worth the last two years.
I guess I was just...
so sick of being
pissed off all the time
and not doing anything about it.
That's still crazy.
But I'm a coward. too.
I only really stayed with Brian
because my dad was dying...
Died.
Lung cancer. last year.
And I was just...
just so scared to be alone.
I'm sorry.
Really. I didn't know.
Well. you don't know
me. either. Gina.
Oh. my God. I thought this road
was supposed to be cleared.
Yeah. it is. if you're
going out of the city.
but we're going in.
Want to test your theory?
Stop the vehicle!
No! Slow down!
Ah!
Oh. God.
Oh.
Do you know what sucks?
Hmm?
We're still cowards.
I left Brian and you
told me off. but...
But we kept stealing the tanker
because we're both
really scared.
After everything. I'm
still really scared.
Me too.
Blair. look.
What are they doing?
What are you doing?
Oh. my God.
- Ah!
- What are they?! Go! Go!
We're not cowards.
Get your lighter out!
Get out of your cars!
Run!
Is it getting them?
Yes. yes. yes!
Light it!
Are you kidding me?! No!
The one time we need it to blow!
The one time!
Yeah. We got to
light something else.
It's my lucky thing! Blair!
No! Really?! Okay!
Come on.
Ow.
We made it to 5:00.
We made it.
We made it. It's past 5:00.
Do you think we're dead?
'Cause I really
wanted to see my dad.
No.
No. we're not dead.
I think...
that you have a
personality disorder
and you passed it to me.
What?
Yeah.
Well. people spend more
time with their co-workers
than their own families.
It makes sense that we'd meld...
Ow... too much.
Ow. my wrist.
You think I infected you with
my... with my personality?
It's a thing.
It's... I read about it.
Folie à deux.
None of this is real.
Ow.
We ended up at the
same gas station.
facing the most traumatic
of life-altering
experiences together.
And then. now we're
sharing a delusion.
Yeah. you'd rather invent a
psychosis than agree with me.
I didn't invent a...
It's... It's a real thing.
None of this is real. but...
Okay... the disorder is real.
Alright. okay.
Let's go get your nieces.
Yeah?
Aah.
Ah.
You know that neck accessory
was featured in Vogue.
Is it wrong that I
felt kind of good
when I heard that I ate you?
Uh...
I was gonna ask you about that.
What was it like?
Didn't happen.
Do you know?
It isn't real.
Gina!
Oh. wait. Wait. wait.
For Jasmine.
She's gonna love it.
What sort of terrible
thing would frighten
a little girl so much that
she hides from her own mother?
You'll die without me.
I have Brooke.
What are you doing? Shh.
Go straight for the head. okay?
I can't! You have to!
Now I am going to take
us away from here...
Someplace safe. okay?
You did this. You sick...
Lydia!
Mama!
Who's there?!